(Sheldon:)Who's Nowitzki?
- I'm Nowitzki.
- Oh, you want me to share credit?
(Leonard:)Uh-huh.
(Sheldon:)Get out.
- Oh, hey. Hi.
RAMONA: Oh, bite me.
(Ramona:)Sisters?
(Girl(arriving):)Excuse me, Dr. Cooper.
I'm Kathy O'Brian.
(Girl:)I just finished reading your paper...
(Girl:)...reconciling
the black hole information paradox...
(Girl:)...with your theory of string-network
condensates, and it took my breath away.
(Sheldon:)Maybe when I publish it,
I'll include an inhaler.
(Kathy:)Would you possibly have any time
for me to pick your brain?
(Sheldon:)Let's see. Today's Thursday.
(Sheldon:)Thursday nights
I eat pizza from Giacomo's.
(Sheldon:)- Sausage, mushrooms, light olives.
- Great. I'll bring it to your place.
(Kathy:)I have the address.